sportingz.com 2019-05-27

# Privacy Policy - Sportingz

Below you will find the privacy policy for Sportingz.com (the “website”) which details all of the procedures and policies surrounding the collection, use and disclosure of your information. Within this privacy policy we will refer to the users of the website as “you” or “them” and refer to Sportingz as “we”, “our” or “us”. Within this privacy policy we also detail the services, content and features that we offer which we will refer to as the “services”. The privacy of our users is extremely important to us which is why we will continuously keep our privacy policy up to date. We reserve the right to change this privacy policy, without given notice, at any time in order to protect our visitors. Please ensure you check the privacy policy regularly for any changes.

Privacy policy of Sportingz.com was last updated: January 1st, 2016

**What does this privacy policy cover?**

You will find a whole range of information within this privacy policy, surrounding the collection, usage and disclosure of your information. We will detail our treatment of any personally identifiable information (personal information) and of non-personally identifiable information. We will also detail our treatment of any other information gathered when you our using our services. Any personal information shared by or with our business partners will also be covered within this privacy policy.

What this privacy policy does not cover are any third party applications or third party websites that can be accessed through Afternoon Special. Any third parties that we do not control or own will be governed by their own privacy policies and we accept no responsibility for their policies, practices, content or services. If you do visit a third party application or third party website then we recommend reading through their own privacy policies and terms.

After reading through this privacy policy please ensure you become accustomed with our terms of use and DMCA policy also.

**What information do we collect?**

In order to improve and personalize your experience of the website we do collect some information from our users. We may request or collect the following information from our users at any time:

Personally Identifiable Information (Personal Information) – The only personally identifiable information we may ever request from users of Sportingz.com will be an e-mail address. This is in order to further enhance your experience on the website by sending out newsletters. You do not have to provide this information to us at any time, although this does mean we will be unable to provide you with the newsletter service.

Non-Personally Identifiable Information – When you interact with the website and use our services, we may collect non-personally identifiable information from you automatically. This information is not able to identify you or any personal information about you. Data may include browser type, screen resolution, etc. This information is purely used for analytical and aggregation purposes, to help us further improve the website and the services we provide.

**How is collected information used?**

The first and most important point to stress is that Sportingz.com will never sell or rent the information collected to any third parties. Below is a detailed explanation of how any collected information may be used (both personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable).

Personally Identifiable Information (Personal Information) – The only time we will ever use this information is to provide the newsletter service to you. This personal information will never be sold, shared or rented to any third parties. We believe our newsletter service provides an enhanced experience of the website, however it is not compulsory to provide this information to Sportingz.com.

Non-Personally Identifiable Information – This information is not able to identify you or any personal details about you and is used solely for analytical and aggregation purposes. We use this information to learn about different behavior and patterns of our users, including what type of content they like and dislike. We may sometimes share this information with third parties and advertising partners in order to tailor the type of advertisements you see on the website. This further enhances your experience of the website, by showing you the type of content that you enjoy. This non-personally identifiable information is completely stripped back of anything which may personally identify you in any way.

Protection – We reserve the right to disclose any information we feel necessary for the protection of us and our users. We may access, read, keep and disclose anything reasonably necessary in order to:

  * Satisfy any applicable laws, governmental request, regulations or legal processes
  * Detect, prevent or address any security, technical issues or fraud
  * Enforce our terms of service, breaches of which can be found in our terms of use; this includes investigation of any potential violations of our terms
  * Respond to queries from users or respond to support requests
  * Protect all of our rights, our users, the public, our property and our safety.

This may include exchanging information with third party companies in order to address any safety or technical issues or to prevent spyware and malware.

**What are your privacy choices?**

Using this website safely and securely is of paramount importance. Therefore it is important that you understand your privacy choices and what how you can decide what happens to your information. Below are the choices you have in regards to your privacy:

  * You can choose at any time not to give us any personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address. It is not mandatory to provide this information but we are unable to provide a newsletter service to those who do not provide an email address.
  * You can choose to have your personally identifiable information removed from our database at any time. Please note that you will no longer be able to access our newsletter if you choose to have this information removed. You can ask for this information to be removed by sending us an email using the contact details at the bottom of this page.
  * You can choose to manage cookies and stop any of your non-personally identifiable information from being collected by us and the website. More information on cookies can be found below.
  * You can choose not to access any third party applications or websites from Sportingz.com.

**Information on cookies**

We rely on the use of cookies in order to enhance the website and our services for our users. A cookie is a tiny piece of data that any website can store on the device you use to access it, including mobile phones, tablets and computers. This cookie is then used in order to recognize you when you return. Cookies can keep a note of your likes, dislikes, browsing preferences and choices for their return. In order to personalize and enhance your experience we may use cookies in the following ways:

  * To remember any of your preferences when you are browsing the website.
  * To customize the content and advertisements that we may provide throughout the website.
  * To research and measure how effective our service is.

Cookies do not provide us with any personally identifiable information and can be declined at any time. If you wish to turn off cookies then please refer to your browser’s instructions. Please note that disabling cookies may impact the experience you have on our website.

**Third Parties**

There may be times in which we allow third party vendors to access the cookies provided by you, the user. This is in order to personalize your experience on the website. Third party vendors, such as Google, may use this information gathered in order to tailor your experience on other websites and on this website; this includes displaying relevant content and advertisements. Google uses the DoubleClick cookie, which will allow it to present users with advertisements based on the visits to our site and/or other websites that you may have visited elsewhere online. Advertisements provided are based on your interests and preferences, your likes, dislikes and other information picked up from the cookies. The same also applies to partners of Google. As a user of the website you are able to opt out of DoubleClick cookies, and any relevant advertising, at any time by visiting one of the following:

We do allow third party vendors to use cookies, web beacons, and other reasonable tracking tools, in order to collect information from the website. This is managed in the same way that third party vendors do for other websites online. These third party vendors are only allowed to use the information collected for measurement, analytics and targeted advertisement services.

As well as third party vendors we may also contain links to third party websites in order to provide you with even more content that we think you may enjoy. We do not own or control these third party websites and so our privacy policy does not govern the content on these sites. Please ensure you read through any third party website’s own privacy policy and terms before accessing their content. We cannot be held responsible for any content or policies of third party websites.

**Opt-Out**  
We partner with third party advertisers to serve and display advertising on the Services. These partners may use cookies and Web beacons to collect information about your activities across different websites and services to provide you with relevant advertising. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by clicking [here](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/#!/). To serve and display advertising relevant to your location, the Services may also track your device’s precise geolocation by responding to beacons or inaudible signals sent to your device’s microphone. If you do not want the location of your device to be tracked by the Services, please opt-out using your device settings.

**Questions or concerns?**

If you are confused about anything found within this privacy policy then please feel free to drop us an email at info@Sportingz.com . Please include the details of any of your concerns and we will get back to you with a detailed response.
